Humpty Dumpty will reach the target area
in approximately five hours.
And what about Westcott?
Just as expected.
He hasn't moved from
the hotel in Tengu City.
A girl thinks, "If only I was more honest."
A girl wishes, "If only I had more courage."
Wish upon a shooting star.
"Episode Five:
'Despair Comes Crashing Down'"
Maybe we went a bit too far...
I didn't think she'd be that upset...
No, it's not as bad as you think.
Her mental state, mood, and happiness...
All have risen above the most severe level.
She's probably not used to getting
compliments when she isn't transformed.
Despite wanting to be acknowledged
from the bottom of her heart,
she has zero self-confidence.
Now that you mention it,
Natsumi was saying nobody
ever paid attention to her.
Sounds like a few bad experiences
have warped her idea of self-worth.
Beauty isn't the issue here.
Isn't it whether or not someone
accepts Natsumi for who she is?
Those guys, saying all those lies...
Haniel.
I'll find out the truth.
Tohka, Yoshino...
Hmm?
Hello.
Are you taking a break, too?
Hey, what do you two think?
About that one Natsumi girl.
Think, meaning?
How disgusting can that Natsumi get?
She's so ugly, it's not even funny, right?
Kotori, what's the matter?
This isn't like you.
Eh?
U-Um, I don't think Natsumi
is disgusting at all.
Yeah, yeah!
Wh-What are you talking about?
When she's that much of a
disgraceful mess, it's an eyesore.
Huh? What's going on here?
What's up, Kotori?
You don't seem yourself today.
Get this, guys. They're
saying weird things...
Doubt. What weird things?
That Natsumi is pretty and she's
not a pain to take care of...
Eh?
I think the one saying weird things is you.
Puzzled. That doesn't sound
like something you'd say.
You shouldn't be talking
about Natsumi like that!
--No way, it can't be... This means...
--That's such a funny face!
Hey, Kotori?
Whoa!
Kotori? Sorry, are you okay?
You seem down. What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong, all right?
By the way, about Natsumi and her meals...
At last, here comes the truth...
I'm wondering if we should
let her out of the room.
Eh?
I've been giving it
a lot of thought, and well...
She's gotta be lonely eating alone like that.
But if she ate yummy meals
with everyone else,
I think Natsumi might warm up to us.
Hey, what's the matter?
Did I say something weird?
Shut up, you idiot!
Hey, Kotori!
Her leaving candy behind is unthinkable...
What happened to her?
Kotori?
What's up with you?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Anyways, there's an emergency.
Natsumi... She escaped from the facility.
It's no use...
I looked everywhere, but no sign of her!
I doubt she's here, but...
Natsumi!
Thank goodness, here you--
You're...
Pardon me for intruding.
Ellen?! What are you doing here?!
Well, well. What does the great
DEM want with little old me?
I came to ask you a question.
A question?
Yes...
The spirit you took away
the other day, Witch...
Where is she now?
There's no way I'm telling you that!
Is that so?
What a nice house.
I imagine you're all like
one happy family here.
That happy family... Do you want to lose it?
I'll ask one more time.
In exchange for the safety
of the other six Spirits,
tell me where I can find Witch.
Any reaction from Natsumi?
None at Point A.
Same for Point B.
Not good...
If she's wary of us and refuses
to show herself again...
Hmm? This reaction...
Natsumi?
No, but it's peculiar...
It could be a satellite based
on its altitude and trajectory.
That's odd. Why would something like--
Commander!
There's magical power, but it's faint...
It's... an explosive magic!
Enlarging the image!
Bandersnatch...
I see...
Don't tell me...!
Yes.
Very well.
I'll handle things here.
Today's your lucky day, Shido Itsuka.
Have you found Natsumi?
Nope... Had a bit of trouble...
Shido, I need you to listen.
You're not going to believe this, but...
...in a dozen or so minutes,
a satellite will crash into Tengu City.
H-Hold on a second! What do you mean?!
I'll explain later. It's dangerous
to be above ground.
Get yourself to the nearest shelter.
But Tohka and them?!
Don't worry. Where they're at,
the debris won't leave a scratch.
Debris?
Yeah. We're blasting it to smithereens.
Keep searching for Natsumi
as long as you can.
But if you can't find her,
evacuate before it's too late.
Yeah, all right.
I'm counting on you, Shido.
Kotori...
What?
Thank you.
That's my line.
"Spatial quake alarm official announcement"
--I'm scared
--It's over here! This way!
Natsumi! Natsumi!
"Spatial quake alarm official announcement"
Please, answer if you hear me! Natsumi!
Debris from a satellite is about
to come crashing down!
It's dangerous to be out here!
Let's get to an underground shelter!
If you don't know where
to go, just follow me!
"Spatial quake alarm
official announcement"
Got it, Natsumi?!
We won't shut you in a room anymore!
When this is over, you can
go wherever you want!
Please!
Why do you go this far?
The one you're searching for...
is just the real me.
I was trying to ruin your life...
I erased your friends...
I did those terrible things...
So why do you care about me so much?
Natsumi!
Commander! The satellite!
It's time... Calculate the impact area!
Roger!
Ready? Let's blow it out of the sky.
Natsumi!
Natsumi! Are you around here?!
I'm right here! I'm right--
Mistilteinn, fire!
Why?!
That's odd...
I can't imagine mere Bandersnatch Territory
deflecting Mistilteinn like that.
What the...?!
Bombardment from 12 o'clock.
Displaying now!
That's...
Commander!
Right now, we can't...
Kannazuki, you're in charge here.
Commander.
Now then, shall we begin?
Our war, that is.
Camael.
Megiddo!
Here I go.
Gungnir!
Fire!
Get it?
Target eliminated! Success!
--Woohoo!
--Yeah!
I-It's a satellite!
Another satellite has appeared!
Camael!
Commander!
Commander, any more and...
Kotori, that's...
A second one. We'll recover you
with Fraxinus, so stay put for now.
And the shelter?!
You can't mean... But I haven't yet...!
Please.
Among the lives you want to save,
please let yours be one!
Shido?
Shido?! Shido!
What's going on here?
Um, what's happening?
In a little pinch, are we?
What a sad sight... To get
this flustered over nothing...
Agreement. Try to remain calm.
So is that the satellite then?
Y-You guys...
Kotori, I'm not seeing Shido anywhere.
Shido is...
Kotori, talk to me.
Can we do anything to help?
Please, you guys... My...
Please protect my one and only brother!
It's up to me then...
Power... Lend me your power, Sandalphon!
With this, I can...
Shido!
Y-You guys!
Why are you here?!
Well, Kotori said you were
in trouble, so we had her send us!
I see... And Kotori?
They're busy fighting the enemy airship.
Though, I think they'll be able
to handle it on their own.
Sorry, I honestly thought I'd be a goner.
Guess they took it to the next level.
Outrage. Can't they read the mood?
We won't let them do as they please!
Ike!
Ellen? How nice of you to come.
More importantly, you should leave at once.
The board of director rebels are trying to--
I know that.
Then why are you...?
Because I believe they will fail.
All right.
Just in case, let's send her to the scene.
Her?
It'll be a test of sorts.
Gabriel, March!
It's... incredible!
I knew I liked this song.
I'm getting so pumped up!
Might. Nice assist.
Great!
Tohka, help me out!
Let's destroy that hunk of junk!
We can do it together!
No, we can't.
Can't? Why can't we?
I don't know the details, but that has
some sort of explosive magic on it.
Unless we destroy it higher up...
Have you forgotten who we are?
We're hurricane children who mow
everything down, the Yamai sisters!
Pledge. We'll cast it
aside like it's nothing.
--C'mon!
--Might!
Take this!
Ouch!
Whoa there!
Tohka, the others!
Bastards!
Tohka!
You okay?!
Let's go!
Right!
It's okay.
It'll all work out somehow.
Just like it did that time...
It's okay. Someone will
show up and help them.
Show up already!
Someone will...
Someone will!
Shido!
A lollipop?
N-Natsumi!
Hurry it up.
You're trying to destroy
the big thing, right?
Yeah!
Go on already. Smash it to bits.
B-But that has explosive magic on it!
Hmph! Haniel!
There. Now you can manage it, right?
--Tohka!
--Right!
Was that because of them?
Kaleidoscope!
Natsumi, you're...
What do you think you're doing to Shido?
The only one allowed to tease him...
...is me, don't you know?!
You guys, thank you...
If it was just me, I couldn't
have saved everyone in the city.
Thanks for everything.
Natsumi.
What? Disgusted that I changed into
a lollipop and hid in your pocket?
Or are you upset that I didn't come help--
I'm glad you're okay.
What... are you saying?
I'm the one who hid myself
and watched as you panicked...
And before that, I did
terrible things to everyone!
Why...? Why?
What's your deal? Every last one of you...
Dummies...
H-Hey, Natsumi?
I'm sorry...
Doing all those bad things...
Causing all of you trouble...
When you were all being nice to me...
I was happy, but...
But I couldn't say thank you...
I'm sorry...
Thank... you.
Don't worry about it.
Besides, we'd have been
in trouble if you hadn't come.
Hey, Natsumi.
Remember how I promised
you could go anywhere when it's over?
If you're okay with it,
will you be my friend?
N-Natsumi?!
Darling, you're making
poor Natsumi cry too much.
Eh? But I didn't do anything!
I can't leave Natsumi to someone
who only makes her cry!
So I'll be your friend, too!
That's right! No more teasing Natsumi!
I'll be your friend, too!
M-Me, too!
You can be my kinswoman!
Agreement. We will protect you.
C'mon, you guys! You're making
me sound like the bad guy!
I wasn't teasing anyone to begin with!
Apologize to her!
Gimme a break!
Thank you, everyone...
Um, so...
Hey, Shido.
Do you really... think I'm cute?
Yeah, of course. You're cute, Natsumi.
U-Um...
Teach me how to do makeup?
Sure, you'll get good at it quick.
I see...
Natsumi?
About sealing...
How do we do it?
Eh?
Um, that's...
Eh?!
I guess there's no choice...
You should've warned me
my Spirit armor would disappear!
Shido! What were you thinking
in a place like this?!
Um, I didn't see anything.
Sealing in the middle of a city...
That's one wild fetish.
Agreement.
Using an empty city to play out
your deepest desires is something else.
Darling is a bold one!
What's wrong, Kotori?
Are you serious?!
Huh? What is it, Shido?
Seems like it ain't over yet.
Another bomb is falling down!
I'm out of strength...
...but I've gotta try!
No, it can't be...
Ori... gami?
"Episode Six:
'Crossroads'"